{"data":[{"question":"Earthquakes can damage a tree _________ violently, and it can take several years for the tree to heal.","a":"to cause shaking","b":"when shaking it causes","c":"by causing it to shake","d":"to cause to shake it","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To damage something by doing something\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"_________ bacteria in foods are killed, as they are during baking or stewing, decay is slowed down.","a":"What","b":"The","c":"If","d":"So","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type I: If + simple present, simple future tense","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"The colors and patterns of the wings of butterflies and moths help _________ the organism against predators.","a":"protect","b":"being protected","c":"protecting","d":"protection of","answer":"1","explain":"\u00a0\n- To help(to) do something\n\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"In 1993 the Library of Congress appointed author Rita Dove _________ of the United States.","a":"as was poet laureate","b":"was poet laureate","c":"poet laureate","d":"and poet laureate","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To appoint somebody (as) something: choose someone to do a particular job","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"At the South Pole _________, the coldest and most desolate region on Earth.","a":"Antarctica lies where","b":"where Antarctica lies","c":"Antarctica lies and","d":"lies Antarctica","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use the inversion form with adverb of place at the beginning","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"Tornados, powerful, destructive wind storms, occur most often in the spring when hot winds _________ over flat land encounter heavy cold air.","a":"which to rise.","b":"that rising","c":"are rising","d":"rising","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use V-ing clause to shorten the relative clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"_________ a necessary dimension for measuring astronomical space and the distance of heavenly bodies form the Earth.","a":"Once in time","b":"Time is","c":"The time","d":"It is time","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Narrative: S + V+ O. We need a noun a and a verb to make a complete sentence\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"Jackie Joyner-Kersee, _________ the world record in the heptathlon in the 1988 Olympics, also won the long jump in the year.","a":"whose setting","b":"which she set","c":"whoever set","d":"who set","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use who (personal pronoun) as the subject in the non-defining relative clause","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"The fossilized remains of a type of camel _________ a dog have been found in the Bad Lands of South.","a":"no more large","b":"no larger than","c":"not larger","d":"which no larger","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use no as an adverb (before a comparative adjective)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"Gorillas are quiet animals, _________ they are capable of making about 20 different sounds.","a":"whether","b":"which","c":"even though","d":"as well as","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Even though: as a conjunction to connect two contrast clauses\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"}]}